Guide to the John G. Franclemont papers,1939-1994.
Francelmont, John G. Papers, 1939-1994
- Series: Correspondence Files
  - Nakata, Setsuko, 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Nathan, P. Susai, 1941-1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Nature Company, 1940-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Neil, Kenneth, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Neunzig, Herbert H., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - New York Entomological Society, 1944-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, 1942-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Newman, J.H., 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Newman, L. Hugh, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Nielsen, Mogens C., 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Nye, Ian W.B., 1963-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - O'B-Ox, 1951-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - O'Connor, B.A., 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - O'Neill, Kellie, 1966-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ogata, Masami, 1953-1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Okumura, George T., 1953-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Oman, Paul W., 1956-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ozburn, R.H., 1940-1950 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Pa-Pe, 1949-2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Palm, Charles E., 1941-1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pearson, H.R., 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Pechuman, L.L., 1959-1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Peerless Camera, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Peerless Steel Equipment Co., 1953-1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Pena, Luis, 1947-1953 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Penn, George H., 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Perkins, Ethel, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Perreault, Al and Elaine, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Pettingill, Olin Sewall, Jr., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Pf-Pu, 1941-1995 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Pfaff, E.M., 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Pimentel, David, 1959-1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Plenum Publishing Corp., 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Pohl, Bruno, 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Poole, Robert, 1962-1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Post, R.L., 1940-1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Powell, Jerry A., 1962-1978 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Powers, William O., 1964-1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Q, 1946-1976 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Bernard Quaritch, Ltd., 1946-1977 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Ra-Re, 1948-1983 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Ramberg, Frank, 1969-1998 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Rawlins, John E., 1958-2003 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Rehn, James A.G., 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Reinhard, H.J., 1937-1941 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Reinthal, W.J., 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Reitter, Dr. E., 1950-1968 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Remington, Charles L., 1947-1975 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Revista de Entomologia, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Rh-Ry, 1937-1992 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Richards, Adam Glenn, Jr., 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Richardson, L. Don, 1958-1965 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Riley, N.D., 1948-1955 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Rindge, Frederick H., 1948-1973 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Rings, Roy W., 1962-1971 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Rodeck, Hugo G., 1946-1958 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Roepke, W., 1947-1954 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Rosenberg, W.F.H., 1940-1948 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Ross, Edward S., 1947-1954 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Roth, Vince, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Royal Entomological Society of London, 1949-1996 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Rummel, C., 1939-1942 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1934-1937 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1953-1959 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1961-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Se, 1940-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sabrosky, Curtis W., 1956-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sala, Frank P., 1954-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Schade, F., 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schaefers, George A., 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schmidt, G., 1946-1952 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schroeter, Otto, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schuster, Robert O., 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schwardt, H.H., 1948-1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schweitzer, Dale F., 1970-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Scudder, Harvey, 1940-1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sears, Terry A., 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Selman, Charles L., 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Semel, Maurie, 1954-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Seymour's, 1958-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sh-Sl, 1942-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Shadle, Albert R., 1940-1948 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Shaffer, Jay, 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Shapiro, Arthur M., 1968-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Shaw, Frank, 1953-1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Sherman, Dr. John D., 1941-1957 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Shields, Oakley, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Shower, John A, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sieker, William, 1940-1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Sm-Sz, 1938-1989 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Claude I., 1948-1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Edward H., 1958-1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Eric H., 1969-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Smith, F., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Smith, J. Raymond, 1949-1960 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1946-1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Smyth, J. Adger, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Snyder, Karl D, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Sobatka, Eric, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Society for the Bibliography of Natural History, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Southern California Academy of Sciences, 1950-1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Southwestern Research Station, 1955-1966 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Sperry, John L., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Spilman, T.J., 1954-1976 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Stallings, Don B., 1948-1955 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Staples, John, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Stechert-Hafner Service Agency, 1941-1967 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Steffan, W.A., 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Stehr, Frederick, 1962-1981 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Sternitzky, R.F., 1940-1974 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Stewart, T.D., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Stone, Alan, 1944-1967 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Sugi, Sugero, 1952-1971 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Sweadner, Walter R., 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Swets and Zeitlinger, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Swezey, O.H., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Ta-Ty, 1940-1988 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Tams, W.H.T., 1938-1950 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Tauber, Maurice, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Tilden, J.W., 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Todd, Ed, 1953-1977 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Tomita, G.A., 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Townes, Henry, 1947-1960 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Townes, Marjorie, 1941-1968 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Townsend, A.C., 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Transvall Museum, 1951-1964 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Truab, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Travis, B.V., 1964-1980 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Treat, Asher, 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Triplehorn, Charles A., 1968-1978 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Tripp, Henry, 1950-1972 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Thorne, Fred, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Tulloch, George S., 1949-1962 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - U, 1941-1984 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - U.S. National Museum and Smithsonian, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - V, 1941-1982 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Valley, Karl, 1970-1981 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Van Buskirk, Michael D., 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Vaurie, Patricia, 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Vazquez, Leonila, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Viette, P., 1949-1977 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Viti, Harry C., 1946-1951 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Wa-We, 1939-1996 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Wagner, David, 1983-1996 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Wallesz, David P., 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Walsh, John F., 1969-1979 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 1940-1980 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Watson, Allan, 1964-1983 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Weems, H.V., Jr., 1956-1990 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Weisman, Donald M., 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Weiss, Harry B., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Wenzel, R.L., 1942-1969 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Wepf and Company, 1946-1960 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Werner, Floyd G., 1961-1972 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - West, D.A., 1962-1982 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Weymarn, Michael A., 1938-1942 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Wh-Wi, 1940-1982 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Wharff, Joseph H., 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Wheldon and Wesley Limited, 1948-1995 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Whitcomb, Willard, 1948-1953 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Wielgus, Ronald S., 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Wiggins, Glenn B., 1953-1979 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Wilcke, H., 1948-1953 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Wilde, Gerald, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Wilkinson, Ronald S., 1943-1975 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Will Corporation, 1943-1956 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Willahan, Elaine and Pat, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Wille, J.E., 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Willink,A., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Wilson, E.O., 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Wilson, Francis H., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Wilson, Kent H., 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Winchester Repeating Arms Company, 1947-1955 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Wind, Robert G., 1940-1950 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Wo-Wy, 1949-1987 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Wongsiri, T., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Wright, A. H., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Wyatt, Alex K., 1935-1968 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Y, 1958-1995 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Yankovsky, Alexander, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Yepez, F. Fernandez, 1949-1972 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Young, David, Jr., 1941-1958 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Z, 1941-1982 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Carl Zeiss, Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Zerkowitz, Albert, 1946-1962 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Zimmerman, Elwood C., 1949-1966 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Zoological Society of London, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - No Surname, 1941-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Items: Correspondences with Unknown Senders, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Series: Publications Correspondence
  - Curwen Press (Moths of America North of Mexico), 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dominick, R. B. Part I, 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dominick, R. B. Part II, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dominick, R.(Richard) B. Part III, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Charles R. Edwards and Wedge Collection Records - Collector vs. Owner (Ethics), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Basil Harley Editorial Files, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Monagham and Walsh Publication Files, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Monagham and Walsh Publication Files, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Monagham and Walsh Publication Files, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Monagham and Walsh Publication Files (Franclemont Fascicle 20), 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Munroe, E. G. (Moths of North America) Publication Files, 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Series: Publications Galleys
  - Franclemont Galleys, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Series: Reprints
  - Franclemont, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Andersen-Brown, 1967-1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - A. Blanchard, 1963-1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Chen-Fallas, 1922-1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Ferguson, 1972-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Forbes-Gressitt, 1932-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Grote, 1868-1895 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Heppner-Hinton, 1947-1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hogue, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Imby-Kim, 1922-1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Koçak, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Koponen-Kyrki, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Lafontaine, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Laporte-Øgaard, 1956-1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Parenzan-Pinker, 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Plante, 1975-1986 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sanjean, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Sharplin, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sulcs-Viette, 1898-1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Series: Professional Papers
  - Pacific Science Association Lists of Entomologists of the Pacific Area, 1956-1961 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Biosciences Information Service: Biosis UK, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Bio Scene (Newsletter) biosis U.S., 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Elytron(Newsletter) Coleopterists' Soceity, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Lambillionea (Union Des Entomogistes Belges [Newsletter]), 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Michigan Entomological Society Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Royal Entomological Society of London:Proceedings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - "Systema Naturae" Newsletter, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Systematic Zoology Newsletters, 1949-1963 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - TIEG Newsletter (Teen International Entomology Group), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Xerces Society Letter, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Zoo Scene (Newsletter), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - ARS-ERD Grant, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture Proposal: Franclemont, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal Evaluations Part I, 1959-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal Evaluations Part II, 1968-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal Evaluations Part III, 1977-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Natural History of the Northeastern Bio-Region Literature Preservation Project, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Series: Subject File
  - Biosis - Zoological Record - (Lepid.), 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Collection and Preservation of Insects, 1892-1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pheromones and Biomedical Research Products, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Whole Mounts of Insects, 1934-1953 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cladistics, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cladistis - Dinosaurs, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Evolution of Insect, Fossil etc., 1934-1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Taxonomy - Discussion Group, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Series: Cornell File
  - Degree Requirements, etc., 1952-1962 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Course 218 - Second Library Assignment, NA (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Course 218 - Third Library Assignment, NA (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Course 218 - Fourth Library Assignmnet, NA (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Course 218 - Examinations, 1953-1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Course 218 - Notes, 1931-1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Course 234 - Study of Lepidoptera, NA (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Entomology 533, 1955-1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Entomoogy 533 II, NA (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Entomology 632. Larvae - Lepidoptera, NA (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Entomology 633 Lepidoptera, NA (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Entomology 633, NA (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Entomology 633 II, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - North American Lepidoptera Course Materials, 1933-1939 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lepidoptera Course Materials, 1917-1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - General Entomology Course Notes, NA (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - General Entomology Course Notes II, NA (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - General Entomology Notes, NA (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneouse Items: Notes, 1940-1984 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Canadian National Collection, Ottawa. Loans Returned, 1964-1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Loans from Franclemont Colection, 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Entomology Holdings, etc., NA (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Field Trip Notes, 1969-1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Loans, NA (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Bookbinding, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Common Names of Insects, 1946-1959 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Types + Type Nomenclature, 1928-1961 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Proceedings of the Entomological Club 1837-1838, NA (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Topographic Maps, Ithaca Vicinity, etc., NA (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Topographic Maps, Indices, NA (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Life Membership in the Alumni Association of the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Personal Receipts, 1957-1982 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Oversized Prints [1 broadside 1984, 1 leaflet 1987, 1 print 1989], 1984-1989 (Folder 1)
  - Cornell General: By-Laws, miscellaneous announcements, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - University Faculty, 1953-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - College of Agriculture 1953-1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - College of Agriculture 1959-1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Department of Entomology and Limnology Memoranda 1952-1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Entomology Department and Library 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Entomology Department: Obituaries, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University Entomology Department. Yearbook, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Entomology Department. Stockroom Committee 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Items: Photographs, NA (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Series: Miscellaneous
  - Personal, 1938-1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Letters of Reference. Confidential (Restricted) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Employment related (Restricted) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Personnel. Confidential (Restricted) (Box 11, Folder 3)